SMRUTIREKHA PATTAJOSI

E: smruti.rekha.sai@gmail.com

P: 919556590083

A: Bangalore, India 560076

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Logical Customer support expert bringing 8 years of experience in consistently enhancing customer satisfaction. Poised when communicating with customers and vendors, analyzing and resolving complex issues and documenting accurate notes of account interactions. Versatile professional comfortable working in high-volume, high-stress environment.

WORK HISTORY

Accenture Solution Pvt. Ltd - Customer Support Executive Hydrabad • 09/2019 – Till date

- Working as service compliance expert for validating content to be uploaded by the American client, BYTE DANCE LTD(TIKTOK)
- Adhere to strong compliance policy set by the client and delivered 100% adherence YOY.
- Utilized crisis management techniques to offer corrective solutions and maximize customer satisfaction.
- Created spreadsheets using Microsoft Excel for daily, weekly and monthly reporting.
- As Sr. Member, always tried to support new joiner to make them understand the SOPs of the process and ensured right hand hold to them
- Built strong relationships with operations team to support business process opportunities and improve service.
- Received various accolades from higher leader for demonstrating excellent client service

Tech mahindra - Customer Support Executive

Hyderabad • 10/2018 - 02/2019

- Worked for UIDAI client for Adhaar process to update corrective KYC details to the client prescribed tools.
- Listened to customer's questions and concerns to provide answers or responses.
- Utilized client compliance policy and techniques to offer corrective solutions and maximize customer satisfaction.
- Provided excellent customer service by efficiently resolving issues and responding to inquiries.

Karvy BPO - Senior Executive

Bhubaneswar • 03/2015 - 08/2016

- worked support executive for Airtel process to support customer to avail various offers.
- used various client information updating tools to capture right information to the system.
- Provided customers with updates and periodic statements on

SKILLS

IT SKILLS:

- Operating Systems: C,C++..net Networking,Java,Javascript etc.
- Office application: MS Office 2000/ XP /2007,Window 7

Strengths:

- Excellent communication skill
- Customer Service and Assistance
- Client Satisfaction
- Client Needs Assessment
- Complaint Resolution

EDUCATION

Gandhi Engineering College, Biju Pattanaik Unvrsty

Bhubaneswar • 06/2012

MCA: Computer And Information Sciences

7.2 GPA/CGPA

Dayavihar College, Utkal University

Puri • 07/2009

Bachelor of Science: Science Education

CHSE, A D Mohavidyalaya

Puri • 07/2006

+2 Science: Science Education

Biswambhar Bidyapitha

Puri • 07/2004

10th Exam: All Subject

service developments and changes in trends.

- Managed customer service effectiveness by monitoring performance and assessing metrics.
- Collected customer information and analyzed customer needs to recommend potential products or services.

Magus Customer Dialog - *Customer Developer Executive* Hyderabad, india • 05/2013 - 10/2013

- Worked as service executive for Airtel digital TV process to offer right plan to the customer.
- managed customer requests and provided right resolution by suggesting them appropriate offers to achieve highest level of client satisfaction.
- Carried out day-to-day duties accurately and efficiently.
- Learned new skills and applied to daily tasks to improve efficiency and productivity.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

• PROJECT NAME: PLACEMENT ALERT SYSTEM.